[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "Do you think President Obama is going to announce anything on Thursday which will get America back to work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "I think he's going to announce a number of projects, a number of things that will put America back to work.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Thursday"], "PERSON": ["Obama"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "You seem to be very well-informed on what the president may be saying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "Well, I haven't had any involvement in the speech, itself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "Do you think that he has it in him to come up with a plan which is going to be big enough, radical enough and effective enough to really transform this jobs crisis?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "RB", ",", "JJ", "RB", "CC", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "RB", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "I mean, look at the background.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "Did you agree with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Well, in many ways they don't play by the rules.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "So where does employer, American employer, responsibility kick in here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "They have a significant responsibility that they haven't been taking up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "Everyone over $1 million a year, I'm going to tax the hell out of you, because we need revenue, we need this economy back on its feet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "$", "CD", "CD", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "We do need the revenue.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$1 million"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "Congressman, you're not very impressed then by what you think may be coming?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "We want our president to succeed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Fed"]}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "What kind of thing has President Obama got to come out with to really make a difference here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "Well, I would hope that the president would call on the government's capacity to be able to spend money into circulation, just like the Fed, to create money out of nothing to quantitative easing.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "So, where is the incentives of the Republicans to not play partisan games here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "TO", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "UCINICH: Well, your conventional political analysis is spot-on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "Because -- is it going to be a shoo-in for the president do you think when it comes to it, because no one is quite sure what the GOP stand for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "WP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "All right.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["GOP"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "Could you see a situation where you or somebody else thinks he knows something we need to have a different face here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "CC", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "Well, I'm not a candidate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "WP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "Why doesn't he say, you know something, I'm the president of the United States to John Boehner and if you want to move your thing, you move it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "Well, there is something to what Kipling wrote about if you can keep your head while those about you are losing theirs and blaming it on you, there is something to that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["United States"], "PERSON": ["John Boehner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "Without being too dramatic about it, I mean, could the prospect of a second term of office for Barack Obama hinge on this speech on Thursday?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "Hinge on the speech, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Thursday"], "PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "I mean, slightly rephrasing then, my previous point -- if those jobs are not created, and in fact, if there is continued unemployment and the figure goes up, it is going to be almost impossible, isn't it, for President Obama to win the election?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBG", "RB", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "CC", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "It would be very difficult.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "Is it time for a bit of audacity and hope?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "The obvious question is -- post the killing of Osama bin Laden and other al Qaeda leaders being bumped off, too, are we seeing the end of al Qaeda as an effective terrorist organization?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", ":", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNS", "VBG", "VBN", "RP", ",", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Well, we're certainly seeing them spin out of control in terms of command and control.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Osama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNP", ":", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "Did you ever imagine when you had that extraordinary encounter that he might be capable of pulling off such an atrocity?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "I was fairly certain from the time I met bin Laden -- and this is not revisionist history.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "VBG", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "And it would be almost impossible for a terrorist group now to carry out something that nobody had thought of?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "NN", "RB", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "Well, I think two opposing forces have met there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "Or is it both?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "Well, it is both.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Zawahiri"]}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "What will be going through his mind now, as he tries to regroup and rally his troops, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "CC", "RB", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "Well, al Zawahiri is an interesting man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "But does that kind of sum up really the fact that al Qaeda has managed to bluff the world into thinking that its this incredibly sophisticated, glamorous outfit, when actually it looks like they are just like another bunch of terrorists who may have got lucky a few times?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "Well, I think that it is no secret to any of us that a lot of television production involves bluff.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Qaeda"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["DNI"]}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "POS", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "You guys have to be lucky every minute of every day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "Well, the analysis division in the DNI is the overarching group that has the group of people who prepare the PDA, or the Presidents' Daily Briefing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Qaeda", "U.S."]}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NN", "NNPS", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "Or from everything that you have picked up over the last few years, are there other organizations that you think may -- or even lone individuals that pose a bigger threat?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "MD", ":", "CC", "RB", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "Well, al Qaeda is the key threat to killing Americans on U.S. soil or overseas in rapid operations.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last few years"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Would you think that we need to be finding out pretty quickly who is going to be running these countries?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "RP", "RB", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "Well, power abhors a vacuum.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "What is your personal view, from all that you have seen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "I'm an optimist by nature.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "How does America prepare for this kind of event?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "I think America has been preparing incrementally for ten years since 9/11.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "What is the doomsday event as far as intelligence operatives go, when it comes to this kind of thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "ILLER: Well, I think, as you said a little further back in this show, you're always trying to out-imagine the bad guys.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["DNI", "Director of National Intelligence"]}, "docId": "110906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "DT", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "CC", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "Are you a slightly relieved that you no longer have to have this responsibility bearing down on your shoulders?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "I have to say, the DNI, the Director of National Intelligence, is by and large a policy shop that is meant to lead the intelligence community.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]